Hello friends, welcome to your own
channel Indian Stocks Chart. My name is
Randeep Kaudia and you are watching Chart of
the Day series. Today is
18th November
2023 and today is the second Chart of the Day
friends.
Look friends, this is ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Limited. This is
a company related to the insurance industry. Let's
analyze the chart of ICICI Lombard General Insurance and find out
what targets are coming out. Look
friends, this is a one-day chart. The stock
saw a rise of 2.97%. The stock
slipped from the upper level and recovered from the lower level and
closed at the middle level at 144411 paise. Friends, now let's
stop and take a five-day chart. In the five-day
too, you can see that the trend is a strong
uptrend. If you look at the stock, a
pattern of continuous stress formation is
seen forming and the stock is
trading slightly below its five-day high.
Friends, now let's take a look at the one-month chart.
In one month, you will see the stock trading at 1350  It was
consolidating in the range of 1400 and
in the last of the chart you will see a rising
invert head and shoulders, the stock has
given a breakout above 1400 here and the
stock is trading at its one month high.
Come friends, now let's see the chart
of six months. In six months, if you see, the
low of the stock was below 1100 and from there the
stock crossed 1400 with great speed.
After that majorly you will see the stock
consolidated in the range of 1300-1400 and
you will see that it was facing a resistance of 1400.
This time you will see that the
stock has given a breakout of that resistance also above 1400
and the stock is now trading at its 6
month high.
Come friends, now let's see the chart
of one year. In one year, if you see, the low of the stock is
below 1000 and
now you see that the consolidation that was going on in the stock at the upper level,
in that consolidation the
stock has given a bullish pattern.  The inverted head and
shoulders broke out above 14 here
and the stock is trading at almost its one-year high.
Come friends, let's now look at the chart of the
five year. Come friends, let's
now look at the chart of the five year.
In the five year, you can see that the high of the stock is
above 1500 and a
good decline was seen in the stock, which
brought the stock near 1000. The stock formed
a good consolidation or base formation here in the range of 1000 to 1300
and
seeing its breakout, the stock reached near 1500.
Here you will see the 1400 degree consolidation and after
that consolidation breakout, the
stock is again giving indications of crossing 1500.
Come friends, now let's look at the chart
of the maximum. In the maximum also, you can see
that a downward channel or
flag formation was seen.
From below 1250, the stock reached near 1500. The
stock made a good base formation here above 1400.  Round
consolidation was done and then again the stock
is showing the possibility of crossing 1500. Come friends, let's talk about the
target. See friend, if you give
one to two months time to ICCI Lord General Insurance, then
you will
see targets up to 00 coming in it. Friends, if
you like this video, then subscribe to the channel,
like the videos,
share them. If you have any query, then
tell me by writing in the comment box. If you want to do trading in the stock market,
then you can contact me on my number.
You can
whatsapp me on-web